playerize.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy | SuperRewards

**1\. Terms**

By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.

**2\. Use License**

  1. Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Playerize, Inc's web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not: 
    * modify or copy the materials;
    * use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
    * attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Playerize, Inc's web site;
    * remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
    * transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.
  2. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Playerize, Inc at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.

**3\. Disclaimer**

  1. The materials on Playerize, Inc's web site are provided "as is". Playerize, Inc makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Playerize, Inc does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.

**4\. Limitations**

In no event shall Playerize, Inc or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Playerize, Inc's Internet site, even if Playerize, Inc or a Playerize, Inc authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.

**5\. Revisions and Errata**

The materials appearing on Playerize, Inc's web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Playerize, Inc does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Playerize, Inc may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Playerize, Inc does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.

**6\. Links**

Playerize, Inc has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Playerize, Inc of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user's own risk.

**7\. Site Terms of Use Modifications**

Playerize, Inc may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.

**8\. Governing Law**

Any claim relating to Playerize, Inc's web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to its conflict of law provisions.

General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site.

_Last Updated: December, 24 2014_

Playerize, Inc., trading as SuperRewards, (“ **SuperRewards”/”we”/”us** ”) offers services through the website [www.superrewards.com](http://www.superrewards.com/) (the “Website”) which enable users to participate in surveys, watch videos or sign up for new services all with the aim of receiving rewards from advertising partners (the “SuperRewards Services”).  We respect the privacy and personal electronic communication of users of the SuperRewards Services.  This Privacy Policy sets forth SuperRewards’s policy with respect to personally identifiable data (“Personal Information”) and other information that is collected from users of the SuperRewards Services.    

**By providing us with Personal Information, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Information to the SuperRewards Services, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Information may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of SuperRewards and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in Canada, the United States or other countries as indicated by this Privacy Policy from time to time.**   You may withdraw your consent to our processing of your Personal Information at any time.  However, withdrawing consent may result in your inability to continue using certain features of the SuperRewards Services. 

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the “ **SuperRewards Services** ” include (a) the Internet services operated by SuperRewards including surveys we run from time to time, (b) SuperRewards related portal website and other SuperRewards websites (collectively, “ **Site** ”) and (c) all software made available by SuperRewards in connection with any of the foregoing.  Any new features added to or augmenting the SuperRewards Services are also subject to this Privacy Policy.

Please note that the SuperRewards Services are not intended for minors and SuperRewards does not knowingly collect any Personal Information from anyone under 13 years of age. Currently,   SuperRewards does not share your e-mail address or other Personal Information, such as name, address, gender or age, with third parties for marketing purposes without your prior consent.   In other words, we don’t sell customer lists.  

**What does this Privacy Policy apply to?**

By using the SuperRewards Services or submitting Personal Information to SuperRewards, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the SuperRewards‘s Services. Because our business may change, we reserve the right to update or make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. Your continued use of the SuperRewards Services will signify your acceptance of these changes.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Information collected by SuperRewards other than Personal Information collected through the SuperRewards Services. This Privacy Policy will not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to SuperRewards through the SuperRewards Services or through any other means. All unsolicited information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and SuperRewards shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such unsolicited information to others without limitation or attribution.  

Although the use of non-personal information collected, used or disclosed through the Internet as described herein is not restricted (and to the extent that such is the case, the obligations under this Privacy Policy do not apply to such information), we provide information in this Privacy Policy about the collection of such information for the sake of transparency with respect to the operation of the SuperRewards Services.

**How does SuperRewards collect and use Personal Information?**

We collect Personal Information from you directly when you create an account, provide information to us when signing up to use our survey system and via your corporate partners who may share Personal Information with us.  Now, or in the future, SuperRewards may use Personal Information to create personalized content, or to tailor services and advertising on or related to the SuperRewards Services to individuals identified as likely consumers to benefit from these products or services.  In addition, SuperRewards otherwise uses the Personal Information you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Information for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Information in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Information you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Information in order to obtain access to the SuperRewards Services, we will use your Personal Information to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services.  For example, if you provide demographic data and contact information when you sign up to use our survey system, we will use that information you provide to provide services to you and for other purposes identified in this policy.  

SuperRewards and its subsidiaries and affiliates may also use your Personal Information and other non-personally identifiable information collected through the SuperRewards Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the SuperRewards Services, to better understand our users and to improve the SuperRewards Services. SuperRewards and its affiliates may use this information to contact you in the future to tell you about products or services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to "opt-out" of receiving future communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below.

**Usage Statistics.**  SuperRewards may also compile Personal Information and usage statistics such as usage patterns, traffic patterns on the website and website page views and intereaction. SuperRewards may use this non-personal information (which includes data which is anonymized Personal Information) for statistical purposes to improve the SuperRewards Services and to manage our networks and systems more efficiently, for advertising purposes and share with our corporate customers and partners. Individual users cannot be identified through these reports and analytics.

**Cookies.**  SuperRewards makes use of “cookies,” in order to identify returning users and expedite your reconnection to the network. Cookies are files that can contain specific user information, such as User ID, or they can be used to maintain a connection with you during your visit (so that you can visit pages of a site without retyping the same information over and over). SuperRewards uses cookies to track customer traffic patterns, to maintain a connection during your visit with us, to track your preferences, to diagnose problems on our servers and administer the SUPERREWARDS Services. The SuperRewards Services may make use of a session cookie which expires after a few minutes of inactivity and is automatically deleted from your computer.

**MAC Addresses.**  The SuperRewards Services may also record and retain the MAC (Media Access Controller) address from the network card in or used with your computer or other device to enable SuperRewards to accurately perform billing and administrative functions and otherwise provide the SuperRewards Services.   

**Device IDs.**  Through use of the SuperRewards Services, SuperRewards may have access to the unique device identifier for the smartphone, tablet or other device that you use the services on.  We use this identifier for verification purposes, to customize the services and directly or through partners, serve ads that are more relevant to you, display billing options and a variety of other uses related to the SuperRewards Services.

**Security Measures.**  The SuperRewards Services have security measures in place to protect our users, our users' data, and the integrity of our websites and online Products and Services against intrusion and subsequent loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  SuperRewards recommends that all users familiarize themselves with their browsers, and learn to identify and understand the differences between secure and regular connections and be aware of the implications of transmitting personal information over an insecure connection.

**Security Limits.**  Despite the security measures described above, SuperRewards strongly recommends that its customers take measures to ensure the security of their data across any Internet connection. Like any high-speed service, including DSL and cable, the SuperRewards Services are not inherently secure. We recommend the active use of security solutions such as personal firewalls, anti-virus software, virtual private networks and encryption, though we do not provide these solutions for our users and cannot guarantee their effectiveness. It is the user's responsibility to evaluate their personal needs and workplace requirements, and obtain and properly configure appropriate security measures.

**Tracking Unlawful Use of SuperRewards Services.**  On occasion, it may be necessary to record and trace individual usage and/or personal or technical information in order to maintain the integrity and security of the SuperRewards Services. In order to protect our users and maintain a high level of service, SuperRewards will use commercially reasonable efforts to track and identify any malicious user in contravention of our Terms of Service. To that end, SuperRewards or its representatives may track and record any information that may be considered evidence of misuse. 

**Advertisements:**  Advertisements (including banner ads) appearing through the SuperRewards Services may be delivered by us or one or more third-party web advertisers. These third party web advertisers may set cookies. These cookies allow the advertisement server operated by that third party to recognize your device each time they send you an online advertisement. Accordingly, advertisement servers may compile information about where or whether you viewed their advertisements and which advertisements you clicked on. This information allows web advertisers to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.  The Privacy Policy applies to cookies placed on your device by us, but does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party web advertisers.  For the privacy practices of such third-party web advertisers, you should consult the applicable privacy policy for the relevant third-party web advertiser(s).

**With whom does SuperRewards share my Personal Information?**

SuperRewards is not in the business of selling your Personal Information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below: 

  * **Business Transfers:** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Information may be part of the transferred assets.  
  * **Related Companies:** We may also share your Personal Information with the SuperRewards Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy. 
  * **Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties:** SuperRewards, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function.
  * **Advertisers:** SuperRewards may share Personal Information you provide with advertisers in order to short-cut and pre-populate fields in surveys and for verification purposes (for example, checking your identify before awarding you virtual currency or other rewards).  We do not control advertisers or their collection and use of personal information.
  * **Legal Requirements:** SuperRewards may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of SuperRewards, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the SuperRewards Services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability. 

**What is SuperRewards’s policy regarding links to other sites?**

You should be aware that while you are using the SuperRewards Services you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. Because we cannot control the privacy practices of these websites, we recommend reading the privacy policy of the website you link to before you submit any of your Personal Information. The links from the SuperRewards Services do not imply that SuperRewards endorses or has reviewed such third-party sites.

**How long does SuperRewards keep my Personal Information?**

We will keep your Personal Information for as long as it remains necessary for the identified purpose or as required by law, which may extend beyond the termination of our relationship with you.  We may retain certain data as necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained personal information will remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  If you request that your name be removed from our databases, it may not be possible to completely delete all your Personal Information due to technological and legal constraints.

**How do I ask a question, obtain a copy of my Personal Information or file a complaint?**

To keep your Personal Information accurate, current and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Information in our possession that you have previously submitted via the SuperRewards Services.  

If you want to verify the accuracy of the Personal Information we hold about you and to have a general account of our uses of that information, you may request the same in writing (see further Contact Details below) and we will provide you with a copy of your Personal Information although in certain limited circumstances, we may not be able to make all relevant information available to you such as where that information also pertains to another user.  In such circumstances we will provide reasons for the denial to you upon request.  We will endeavour to deal with all requests for access and modifications in a timely manner.

**Contact Details.**  If you have any questions or complaints about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0a7a78637c6b69734a797f7a6f78786f7d6b786e7924696567); or by regular mail at SuperRewards, Inc., Attn: Privacy Officer, to SuperRewards’s main offices located at 180 Sansome, 4th Floor c/o Playerize, San Francisco, CA, 94104.
